#### TRAN HOANG LAM

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER

035-9900-838 | devlamtran@gmail.com

<u>Linkedin</u> | <u>GitHub</u>

## **Objective**

Hi, I'm a Front-End Developer with 2 years of experience. I have a solid background in creating complex web applications, with extensive proficiency in JavaScript. I'm interested in new technology and always strive to improve my skills.

#### **Skills**

Front End: ReactJS, NextJs, Redux, Redux, Vite, Lodash, Tailwind, Boostrap, Ant Design, Typescript, ...

Back End: Rest APIs, Express.js, Prisma, NestJS, ...

**Databases**: SQL (My SQL)

Data Structures and Algorithms: Trie, Hash table, Graph, Binary search tree, ...

Basic Knowledgeable: Docker, VPS, Domain, ...

Tools: Git, GitHub, GitLab, ...

## **Work Experiences**

## **CyberSoft Technology Company Limited**

#### **Front End Developer**

Mar 2023 - Now | ♥ Ho Chi Minh

Participating in the development of e-learning platforms and an ecosystem for automatic CV generation, alongside implementing a Live Coding system, to become the leading programming education center in southern Vietnam.

- Develop an online learning system for thousands of students that keeps them engaged and motivated in their daily studies.
- Researching and implementing new ideas for the company's innovation and development.
- Successfully designing and developing our company's own online coding platform similar to Leet-code and Hackathon.

#### **Teaching**

Jan 2024 - Now | Ho Chi Minh

- Participate in teaching according to the curriculum of the CyberSoft Technology (NodeJS, ReactJS).
- Participate in managing and developing IT projects..

### **Querychart Technology Company**

#### **Front End Developer**

Jul 2022 - Mar 2023 | • Ho Chi Minh

I participated in the development of an application for flowcharts

- Developed several features such as freeform drag-and-drop, zoom in, zoom out for flowchart, and interactive visualization between table and flowchart.
- Code review and learning new technologies.

## **Projects**

## **TechX - Learning Platform | Front End Developer**

Aug 2023 - Now

Team Size: 8

Description: A personalized online learning system designed to optimize individual learning experiences through customized learning paths for each user. The system offers unique features to enhance learning performance and foster interaction and sharing among its members.

Teach Stack: ReactJs, Redux Toolkit, Axios, TailwindCss, ChartJS

My Responsibility:

- Content Recommendation Engine
- Progress Tracking and Analytics
- Personalized Learning Path Generation Social Interaction Features (e.g., discussion forums, chat)
  - Resource Sharing Platform
  - · Gami cation Elements for Engagement

**Coding Interview Practice Platform | Full Stack** 

Mar 2023 - Aug 2023

Team Size: 4

Description: The project involves the development of an online platform dedicated to coding interview preparation, inspired by the success of LeetCode. This platform is designed to empower users to refine their coding skills, master algorithmic challenges, and excel in technical interviews.

Teach Stack: ExpressJs, ReactJs, MySQL, AntD, TailwindCSS, Redux, React Ace editor

My Responsibility:

- Coding Challenge Repository
- Code Editor with Syntax Highlighting
- Solution Sharing and Discussion
- Question Management
- User Management (View user profiles, manage roles)

Link: <a href="https://app.querychart.io/charts">https://app.querychart.io/charts</a>

Compiler Integration for Code Compilation (Backend API)

Flowchart App | Front End Developer

Jul 2022 - Mar 2023

Team Size: 4

Description: An advanced application for creating and analyzing flowcharts with features like freeform drag-and-drop, zoom capabilities, and interactive table-to-flowchart visualization. Querychart enhances productivity and outperforms competitors like Mirosoft and Excel.

Teach Stack: React TypeScript, Material UI, SASS, React Zoom Pan Pinch ...

My Responsibility:

- Develop some new small features (e.g., drag-drop, zoom ...)
- Fix bug and modify in old features
- Work Progress Report
- Provide development suggestions for the product

## **Project**

### Multi-Language CMS Landing Page | Full Stack Link: https://daitiendat.vn

Mar 2024 - May 2024

Team Size: 2

Description: Developed a multi-language website with a landing page. The admin page allows users to edit content and images on the landing page and includes automatic translation from Vietnamese to English.

Teach Stack: ReactJS, Tailwind, Antd, Redux, NestJs, Google Api, Docker, ...

My Responsibility:

- Developed a landing page according to the client's design
- Created an admin page that allows clients to edit content
- Developed an automatic translation feature using Google API
- Provide development suggestions for the product
- Deployed the product to the production environment using Docker and VPS

#### **Education**

# Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology and Education

Major: Electronic Commerce 2018 - 2023

English: 550 Toeic